

# **Gregorius Rafael Widojoko**

**Date of birth:** 18 Jan 1999 | **Nationality:** Indonesian | **Gender:** Male | **Phone number:** 

(+31) 644481623 (Mobile) | **Email address:** gregoriusrw@outlook.com | **Website:** 

https://grafaelw.github.io | LinkedIn: www.linkedin.com/in/grafael-wido |

WhatsApp Messenger: +31644481623 |

Address: Lombokpad 6 - 63, 5641BZ, Eindhoven, Netherlands (Home)

#### ABOUT ME

I am holding a master degree in Artificial Intelligence Engineering Systems/Electrical Engineering from Eindhoven University of Technology with specialization in Control Systems, Signal Processing and Artificial Intelligence. I am confident in my ability to swiftly adapt to new environments and integrate smoothly into teams with commitments to catching up and aligning with colleagues resulting in a harmonious collaboration of research and solving engineering problems.

Challenges, in my view, are opportunities for improvement, and I approach them with a positive mindset, ensuring decisions and changes are born out of clear thinking. As a curious and optimist person, I believe that everything can be achieved by thinking logically and clearly and executing it. With problems arise is where I can excel further. Therefore, I am open to solving any real-world challenges where I can grow further outside academia.

#### WORK EXPERIENCE

9 SEP 2023 - 20 FEB 2024 Eindhoven, Netherlands

#### **STUDENT ASSISTANT EUFLEX**

- 1. Assisting student in the self-study time for:
  - a. Control System (5ESD0 in Q1)
  - b. Mathematics I (5EZA0 in Q1)
  - c. Model Reduction (5LMA0 in Q2)
- 2. Correcting a Model Reduction course project

17 JUN 2019 - 16 AUG 2019 Jakarta, Indonesia

## **INTERN IOT ENGINEER** XL AXIATA

As one of IoT (Internet of Things) business startup incubator in Indonesia, X-Camp by XL Axiata works with several partner companies to provide IoT-based business solutions for business owners. My job there as an intern worker was to provide studies on the ideas of business owners, implemented those into an IoT system and presented the business model canvas for clients.

**Business or Sector** Information and communication | **Department** X-Camp (IoT division) |

Address XL Axiata Tower. Jl. H. R. Rasuna Said X5 Kav. 11 - 12. , Kuningan Timur, Setiabudi Jakarta Selatan, 12950, Jakarta, Indonesia

Website www.xl.co.id

1 SEP 2018 – 1 DEC 2019 Surabaya, Indonesia

### **CHIEF EDITOR** IEEE ITS STUDENT BRANCH

Editing journals, papers and articles which are written in Indonesia, making online bulletins for internal IEEE ITS Student Branch, and helping students or lecturers who want to write a research paper in English.

**Business or Sector** Professional, scientific and technical activities | **Department** Electrical Engineering Department |

Address Aj, B and C building, Kampus ITS Keputih, Sukolilo, 60111, Surabaya, Indonesia | Website www.ieee-its-sb.org

28 JUL 2021 - 31 MAR 2023 Jakarta, Indonesia

**CTO OF ARTIFICIAL INTELLIGENCE SYCOMORA** 

Handle an Al-based healthcare apps start up company, starting from simple chat-bot up to assisting doctors in diagnosis (equivalent to halodoc or alodokter in Indonesia). I work part-time, as all of us are still students, mostly medical doctor students and juniors.

#### EDUCATION AND TRAINING

1 SEP 2016 – 4 SEP 2020 Surabaya, Indonesia

BACHELOR OF ENGINEERING Institut Teknologi Sepuluh Nopember

For the first 2 years, I had learnt the fundamentals of electrical engineering, including engineering mathematics, signal processing, control system theories, algorithms, and discrete structures. The last 2 years of my study discussed a lot of artificial intelligence in embedded electronics, machine vision, intelligence system of electronics, and industrial robotics.

The skills that I actually mastered in are artificial intelligence, computer vision, signal processing, and Internet of Things (IoT). These topics are the topics where I had a lot of practical classes, which I could develop myself in broader scope of computer science, electrical engineering, and applied mathematics.

Address Kampus ITS Keputih, Sukolilo, 60111, Surabaya, Indonesia | Website <a href="https://www.its.ac.id">https://www.its.ac.id</a> |

Field of study Electrical Engineering | Final grade 3,44 | Level in EQF EQF level 6 |

National classification KKNI (Kerangka Kualifikasi Nasional Indonesia) | Type of credits US System Credit Hour (SCH) |

Number of credits 145 | Thesis The utilization of facial expression recognition with cloud computing using AWS

1 FEB 2021 - 31 JUL 2021 Enschede, Netherlands

**PREMASTER IN APPLIED MATHEMATICS** University of Twente

Address Drienerlolaan 5, 7522 NB, Enschede, Netherlands | Website www.utwente.nl

1 FEB 2022 - 15 OCT 2024 Eindhoven, Netherlands

MASTER ARTIFICIAL INTELLIGENCE OF ENGINEERED SYSTEMS (ELECTRICAL ENGINEERING) Technische Universiteit Eindhoven

Address De Zaale, 5600 MB, Eindhoven, Netherlands | Website https://www.tue.nl | Level in EQF EQF level 7

#### LANGUAGE SKILLS

Mother tongue(s): INDONESIA

Other language(s):

	UNDERSTANDING		SPEAKING		WRITING
	Listening	Reading	Spoken production Spoken interaction		
DUTCH	B2	B2	B2	B2	B2
ENGLISH	C1	C1	C1	C1	C1
GERMAN	B1	B1	B1	B1	B1

Levels: A1 and A2: Basic user; B1 and B2: Independent user; C1 and C2: Proficient user

## DIGITAL SKILLS

Data Science | Data Visualization | Internet of Things | Signal Processing

#### Research focus

Artificial Intelligence algorithms: Neural Networks, Bayesian Networks, Genetic Algorithms | Algorithms: Markov chain Monte Carlo, Multi-armed bandits, reinforcement learning | Computer Vision | signal processing and analysis | Data Analysis | Neural Networks and Deep Learning | Control Systems | System Identification | Controller Design | Computational modelling

# **Programming**

Python, R, Julia, Matlab | C / C# / C++ | LaTeX | Javascript(Nodejs, ExpressJs) | Programming: Python, HTML, SQL

## **Data Science Tools**

Tensorflow | Scikit-Learn | Pandas | Jupyter Notebook | FluxML | PyTorch

# Other IT skills

Git | Docker | Linux | Github

# **Microprocessor and Microcontrollers**

RaspberryPi │ ■ Hardware: Arduino uno, mega, due, ESP8266.

# DRIVING LICENCE

**Driving Licence:** B 3 Dec 2024 – 3 Dec 2034